Contact

Lahore 03470882712 (Home)

www.linkedin.com/in/yaseen-afzal-3b2448b0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Web Development
Software Development
C#

Yaseen Afzal

Sr. Dot Net Developer (Tech Team Lead)
Lahore

Summary

Experienced Worker with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in C# Dot net and Angular js, crystal reporting, C# Applications, WPF Applications, Self-hosted Applications, web Api's, Rest Api's, Working on ERP Systems, POS, HR, School Applications. Strong administrative professional with a BS(computer sciences) focused on Computer Science from COMSATS University.

Experience

Point of solutions Software Engineer August 2018 - Present (3 years 2 months) Lahore, Pakistan

freelancer Web Developer June 2016 - Present (5 years 4 months)

Abcdevforce Software Developer July 2018 - July 2018 (1 month) lahore pakistaan

Education

COMSATS University
BS(computer sciences), Computer Science (2014 - 2018)